ABRAR AHMED (ELECTRICAL ENGINEER)



Mandi Chowk, Jamber Khurd, tehsil Pattoki, District KASUR



+92-336-4126086



abrarahmedbhatti@gmail.com

Profile

I am an Electrical Engineering graduate who loves machines, operating machines and designing machines. I want to be part of an esteemed organization for betterment of the organization and to polish my own skills as well. I want to excel on the basis of my skills. I Have experience in the field of POWER GENERATION & POWER DISTRIBUTION.

Education

| BISE Lahore | 2010-2013 |
|---|-------------|
| F.Sc. Pre-Engineering | 927 / 1100 |
| University of Engineering & Technology (UET) Lahore | 2013-2017 |
| B.Sc. Electrical Engineering | 3.02 / 4.00 |

Professional Experience

07.2017 - 12.2017 Nishat Power Limited - (200 MW IPP)

Internee Engineer * Wartsila Generators - 18v46



* Planned Maintenance

Asst. Shift Incharge * JenBacher JGS-420



* Maintain Shift activities

07.2018 - PRESENT NHPL - Nishat Emporium Mall

Trainee Engineer * Power House (Wartsila + CAT)



* 11 kV Substation, Schneider

* Maintenance of Mall Area

Skills

- Good Communication Skills
- MS word, Excel, powerPoint
- Proteus, Adobe

Languages

- English
- ♦ Urdu
- punjabi

References will be furnished on demand.